[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
        "code": "console.log(typeof NaN)",
        "answers": [
            "undefined",
            "NaN",
            "string",
            "number"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de la siguiente expresión?",
        "code": "3 + 2 + '7'",
        "answers": [
            "12",
            "327",
            "57",
            "NaN"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
        "code": "let a = 10;\nlet b = () => {\n  console.log(this.a);\n}\nb();",
        "answers": [
            "undefined",
            "null",
            "10",
            "ReferenceError"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de la siguiente expresión?",
        "code": "1 + 2 + '3' + 4 + 5",
        "answers": [
            "'3345'",
            "15",
            "NaN",
            "Error"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
        "code": "for (var i = 0; i < 3; i++) {\n  setTimeout(() => console.log(i), 1);\n}",
        "answers": [
            "0 1 2",
            "3 3 3",
            "1 2 3",
            "2 1 0"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de la siguiente expresión?",
        "code": "2 > '3'",
        "answers": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "undefined",
            "NaN"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
        "code": "const arr = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];\nconst [x, y, ...rest] = arr;\nconsole.log(rest.length);",
        "answers": [
            "0",
            "1",
            "2",
            "3"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de la siguiente expresión?",
        "code": "'2' + 3 * 4",
        "answers": [
            "212",
            "20",
            "26",
            "Error"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
        "code": "const arr = [1, 2, 3];\narr[10] = 10;\nconsole.log(arr.length);",
        "answers": [
            "3",
            "10",
            "11",
            "undefined"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
        "code": "console.log(0.1 + 0.2 === 0.3)",
        "answers": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "undefined",
            "NaN"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de la siguiente expresión?",
        "code": "[] + []",
        "answers": [
            "[]",
            "''",
            "undefined",
            "NaN"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
        "code": "const obj1 = {a: 'foo'};\nconst obj2 = {b: 'bar'};\nconst obj3 = {c: 'baz'};\nconst obj4 = Object.assign(obj1, obj2, obj3);\nconsole.log(obj4);",
        "answers": [
            "{a: 'foo', b: 'bar', c: 'baz'}",
            "{b: 'bar', c: 'baz'}",
            "{a: 'foo', b: 'bar'}",
            "{c: 'baz'}"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de la siguiente expresión?",
        "code": "'foo' instanceof String",
        "answers": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "null",
            "undefined"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
        "code": "const arr1 = [1, 2, 3];\nconst arr2 = [4, 5, 6];\nconst arr3 = [...arr1, ...arr2];\nconsole.log(arr3);",
        "answers": [
            "[1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6]",
            "[[1, 2, 3], [4, 5, 6]]",
            "[[1, 2, 3], 4, 5, 6]",
            "[1, 2, 3, [4, 5, 6]]"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "¿Cuál es el resultado de la siguiente expresión?",
        "code": "parseInt('0.1')",
        "answers": [
            "0.1",
            "1",
            "0",
            "Error"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "¿Cuál es la salida de este código?",
        "code": "const a = {x: 1};\nconst b = {y: 2};\nconst c = Object.assign({}, a, b);\nconsole.log(c);",
        "answers": [
            "{x: 1}",
            "{y: 2}",
            "{x: 1, y: 2}",
            "{}"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    }
]